Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series LX is arranged in 7 sub-series by Union file number.
Series LXI is arranged in 2 sub-series by Union file number.
Series LXII is arranged in 1 sub-series by Union file number.
Series LXIII is arranged in 33 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series LX. REGIONAL ASSOCIATIONS OF GENERAL CHAIRMEN
  - Sub-Series 349-0. Regional Associations of General Chairmen
    - General. Section 6 Notices, 1958-1959 (Box 522, Folder 1)
    - General, 1929 (Box 522, Folder 2)
    - General, 1938 (Box 522, Folder 3)
    - General, 1933 (Box 522, Folder 4)
    - General, 1932 (Box 522, Folder 5)
    - General, 1930 (Box 522, Folder 6)
    - General, 1924 (Box 522, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 349-1. Regional Associations of General Chairmen
    - Eastern Regional Association, 1956-1962 (Box 522, Folder 8)
      May 1956-62.
    - Eastern Regional Association, 1955-1956 (Box 522, Folder 9)
      1955-April 1956.
    - Eastern Regional Association, 1951-1954 (Box 522, Folder 10)
    - Eastern Regional Association, 1945-1950 (Box 522, Folder 11)
    - Eastern Regional Association, 1940-1944 (Box 522, Folder 12)
    - Eastern Regional Association, 1930-1939 (Box 522, Folder 13)
    - Eastern Regional Association, 1928-1929 (Box 522, Folder 14-15)
    - Eastern Regional Association, 1924 (Box 522, Folder 16)
    - Eastern Regional Association, 1926-1927 (Box 522, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 349-2. Regional Associations of General Chairmen
    - Southeastern Regional Association, 1963-1968 (Box 522, Folder 18)
    - Southeastern Regional Association, 1956-1962 (Box 522, Folder 19)
    - Southeastern Regional Association, 1953-1955 (Box 522, Folder 20)
    - Southeastern Regional Association, 1940-1952 (Box 522, Folder 21)
    - Southeastern Regional Association, 1929-1930 (Box 523, Folder 1)
    - Southeastern Regional Association, 1926 (Box 523, Folder 2)
    - Southeastern Regional Association, 1925 (Box 523, Folder 3)
    - Southeastern Regional Association, 1924 (Box 523, Folder 4)
    - Southeastern Regional Association, 1928-1929 (Box 523, Folder 5)
    - Southeastern Regional Association, 1927 (Box 523, Folder 6)
    - Southeastern Regional Association. Minutes of Meetings, 1931-1932 (Box 523, Folder 7)
    - Southeastern Regional Association, 1931 (Box 523, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 349-3. Regional Associations of General Chairmen
    - Western Regional Association, 1963 (Box 523, Folder 9)
    - Western Regional Association, 1959-1962 (Box 523, Folder 10)
      December 1959-62.
    - Western Regional Association, 1955-1959 (Box 523, Folder 11)
      July 1955-November 1959.
    - Western Regional Association, 1964 (Box 523, Folder 12)
    - Western Regional Association, 1953-1955 (Box 523, Folder 13)
      May 1953-June 1955.
    - Western Regional Association, 1948-1953 (Box 523, Folder 14)
      August 1948-April 1953.
    - Western Regional Association, 1945-1948 (Box 523, Folder 15)
      1945-July 1948.
    - Western Regional Association, 1939-1944 (Box 523, Folder 16)
    - Western Regional Association, 1925 (Box 523, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 349-4. Regional Associations of General Chairmen
    - Express General Chairmen, 1927 (Box 523, Folder 18)
    - Express General Chairmen, 1924 (Box 523, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 349-5. Regional Associations of General Chairmen
    - Joint Regional Association, 1927 (Box 523, Folder 20)
    - Joint Regional Association, 1931 (Box 523, Folder 21)
    - Joint Regional Association.- Policy Committees, 1934-1935 (Box 523, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 349-6. Regional Associations of General Chairmen
    - National Federation of General Secretary-Treasurers, 1935 (Box 523, Folder 23)
- Series LXI. BY-LAWS
  - Sub-Series 376-1. By-Laws
    - Eastern Regional Association of General Chairmen, 1928-1929 (Box 523, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 376-2. By-Laws
    - Southeastern Regional Association of General Chairmen, 1935-1955 (Box 523, Folder 25)
    - Southeastern Regional Association of General Chairmen, 1924 (Box 523, Folder 26)
    - Southeastern Regional Association of General Chairmen, 1928 (Box 523, Folder 27)
- Series LXII. INCREASE IN RATES OF PAY
  - Sub-Series 377-0. Increase in Rates of Pay
    - General, 1924 (Box 523, Folder 28-29)
- Series LXIII. 1928 CONVENTION
  - Sub-Series 382-0. 1928 Convention
    - Proceedings, 1928 (Box 524, Folder 1-12)
      May 14-24, 1928.
    - Report of Grand Lodge Officers, 1928 (Box 524, Folder 13-20)
    - General, 1927 (Box 525, Folder 1)
    - Committee on Company Unions, 1928 (Box 525, Folder 2)
    - General, 1928 (Box 525, Folder 3)
    - Report of Committee on Legislation, 1928 (Box 525, Folder 4)
    - Amendments to Constitution Submitted by Delegates, Local Lodges, and Boards of Adjustment, 1928 (Box 525, Folder 5)
    - Resolutions, 1928 (Box 525, Folder 6)
    - General, 1925 (Box 525, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 382-1. 1928 Convention
    - Articles for Publication in Railway Clerk, 1924 (Box 525, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 382-2. 1928 Convention
    - Souvenir Book, 1927-1928 (Box 525, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 382-4. 1928 Convention
    - General Committee, 1927 (Box 525, Folder 10)
    - General Committee, 1928-1929 (Box 525, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 382-5. 1928 Convention
    - Appeal of Kelly, P.J., 1926 (Box 525, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 382-6. 1928 Convention
    - Mileage and Per Diem Expenses, 1926 (Box 525, Folder 13)
    - Mileage and Per Diem Expenses, 1928 (Box 525, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 382-7. 1928 Convention
    - 1928 Constitution (Box 525, Folder 15)
    - 1928 Constitution, 1926 (Box 525, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 382-8. 1928 Convention
    - Proposed Changes in Brotherhood Laws, 1928 (Box 525, Folder 17)
    - Proposed Changes in Brotherhood Laws, 1926-1927 (Box 525, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 382-9. 1928 Convention
    - Report of Baldwin, H.F., Vice Grand President, 1928 (Box 525, Folder 19)
    - Reports of Grand Lodge Officers, 1927 (Box 525, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 382-10. 1928 Convention
    - Convention Hall, 1927-1928 (Box 525, Folder 21)
    - Convention Hall, 1928 (Box 525, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 382-11. 1928 Convention
    - Delegates, 1928 (Box 525, Folder 23)
    - Delegates, 1926-1927 (Box 525, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 382-12. 1928 Convention
    - Hotel Accommodations, 1928 (Box 525, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 382-13. 1928 Convention
    - Official Call, 1924-1927 (Box 525, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 382-14. 1928 Convention
    - Seating Arrangements, 1928 (Box 525, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 382-15. 1928 Convention
    - Resolutions. Resolution No. 14, 1928-1930 (Box 525, Folder 28)
    - Resolutions, 1928-1929 (Box 525, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 382-16. 1928 Convention
    - Travel Routes, 1928 (Box 525, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 382-17. 1928 Convention
    - Grand Sergeant-at-Arms and Assistants, 1928 (Box 525, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 382-18. 1928 Convention
    - Free Transportation for Delegates, 1928 (Box 525, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 382-19. 1928 Convention
    - Credentials Committee, 1928 (Box 525, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 382-20. 1928 Convention
    - Speakers, 1928 (Box 525, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 382-21. 1928 Convention
    - Daily Printed Minutes, 1928 (Box 525, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 382-22. 1928 Convention
    - Pullman Rates, 1928 (Box 525, Folder 36)
    - Pullman Rates, 1927-1928 (Box 525, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 382-23. 1928 Convention
    - Stenographer for Vice Grand President of Express Division, 1928 (Box 525, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 382-24. 1928 Convention
    - Outer Guards, 1928 (Box 525, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 382-25. 1928 Convention
    - Inner Guards, 1928 (Box 525, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 382-26. 1928 Convention
    - Committee on Rules and Order of Business, 1928 (Box 525, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 382-27. 1928 Convention
    - Board of Tellers, 1928 (Box 525, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 382-28. 1928 Convention
    - Grand Chaplain, 1928 (Box 525, Folder 43)
  - Sub-Series 382-29. 1928 Convention
    - Committee on Committees, 1928 (Box 525, Folder 44)
  - Sub-Series 382-30. 1928 Convention
    - Printed Minutes, 1928 (Box 525, Folder 45)
  - Sub-Series 382-31. 1928 Convention
    - Address of Hon. Davis, J.J., 1928 (Box 525, Folder 46)
  - Sub-Series 382-32. 1928 Convention
    - Resolution of Condolences, 1928 (Box 525, Folder 47)
  - Sub-Series 382-33. 1928 Convention
    - Overtime Pay for Grand Lodge Employees, 1928 (Box 525, Folder 48)